Rapha Maina



Born 19th of March 1999 raphamaina64@gmail.com +254700926561

INTRO

I have a finance degree in Finance and a 1 year experience in financial analysis and risk management acquired from my attachment and work experience. I have a few months of studying and continuously practising coding websites and applications using modern HTML, CSS and Vanilla JavaScript and React js. Building user-friendly and easy to use websites has become a passion that I aim to dig into each day. I actively seek out new technologies and advancements. I can be reached through mail, @ms.Maina001@gmail.com.

WORK EXPERIENCE Account reconciliation

FOC Kenya Supply Chain Management • Mar 2021 - Jan 2022

Attachee

Tower Sacco • May 2019 - Jul 2019

My responsibilities included customer care and front office management, loan appraisals as well as cashier duties.

EDUCATION

ACCA

Star College • Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

ACCA offers business relevant knowledge that is both theoretical and applicable in the modern world and thus a rewarding career in Finance which is what i am aiming for.

Bachelor of Commerce-Finance Option

Taita Taveta University • Jan 2016 - Dec 2020

Certificate of Secondary Education Ndururumo High School • Jan 2012 - Jan 2015

SKILLS

Cash management (company) JavaScript

Github (or other software version management systems) React.js HTML CSS

Account management

CERTIFICATES

Marketing

Certificate offers an overview on marketing research and planning, strategic marketing, digital marketing, digital analytics and social media marketing. • Dec 2020

LANGUAGES

Swahili

Spoken: Fluent • Written: Fluent

English

| ASSOCIATIONS | Green Belt Movement Member |
|--------------|---|
| HOBBIES | Adventure |
| LINKS | https://www.linkedin.com/in/rapha-muthoni-b5ba871b8 |